Guide to Shlomo Narinsky (Neroni) and Sonia Narinsky Postcard Album - Hisham Khatib Collection AD.MC.030_ref174
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
Shlomo Narinsky (Neroni) and Sonia Narinsky Postcard Album - Hisham Khatib Collection
1910-1921
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
Narinsky, Shlomo
Narinsky, Sonia
Jamal Brothers, Jerusalem, Palestine
AD.MC.030_ref174
74 Photographic Prints 74 photogravures over 65 pages of an album. One newspaper clipping.
E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174
Photographic Prints; Palestine; Landscapes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Postcards
- The front cover of the "Shlomo Narinsky (Neroni) and Sonia Narinsky Postcard Album.", Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000001; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Palestine
- The table of contents of the "Shlomo Narinsky (Neroni) and Sonia Narinsky Postcard Album.", Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000002; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
- The text "The Holy Land, 1910-1921 Photogravures by S. Narinsky" by Tim N. Gidal., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000003; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Printed Materials; Biographies; Haifa; Palestine
- (No. 3) The Tower of David (duplicate Ref5)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000004; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Religious Sites; Jerusalem; Buildings; Architecture
- (No. 3) The Tower of David (duplicate Ref4)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000005; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Religious Sites; Architecture; Buildings; Jerusalem
- (No. 53) A Bedouin and his pride (two duplicate portraits of a man with two horses (linked Ref23))., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000006; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Men; Individual Portraits; Palestine; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Horses; Animals
- (No. 14) The River Auja near Jeffa and the place of allied victories Palestine (two duplicate portraits of a man sitting near a tree, with the River Auja (Yarkon River) in the background)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000007; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Jaffa; Rivers; Water; Individual Portraits; Mountains/Hills; Tel Aviv/Tall ʾabīb; Palestine
- (No. 16) The Ruins of Cesarea (a woman carrying a child at the beach at the beach at Qisarya/Cesarea (duplicate Ref38, 58))., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000008; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Coast; Water; Beaches; Women; Children; Group Portraits; Caesarea/Qisarya; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Head Covers/Veils; Postcards; Mediterranean Sea; Seas
- (No. 18) Mountains in Judean desert (Judaean Desert)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000009; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Mountains/Hills; Judaean Desert/Sahara Yahudan; Deserts; Landscapes; Bethlehem; West Bank
- (No. 27) The Mountains of Gilead behind the River Jordan (linked Ref37)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000010; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Jordan River; Jordan; Palestine; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Rivers; Water
- (No. 30) Palm-trees forest near the River Kishon. Haifa. (A landscape of palm trees and hills in Haifa)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000011; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Postcards; Palm Trees; Countryside/Rural; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Haifa
- (No. 33) A Side view of Tiberias (a herd of animals on the shore of Lake Tiberias (Sea of Galilee), as a wagon passes on the adjacent road)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000012; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Animals; Postcards; Sea of Galilee/Lake Tiberias; Lakes; Water; Tiberias/Tabariyyah; Mountains/Hills; Carriages/Coaches; Transportation; Streets/Roads; Goats; Horses; Landscapes
- (No. 39) On the way to Bethlehem (two portraits of people herding sheep)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000013; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Men; Women; Sheep; Animals; Individual Portraits; Streets/Roads; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Musical Instruments; Woodwind Instruments; Mountains/Hills; Cattle/Cows; Agriculture/Farms; Bethlehem
- A studio portrait of a person wearing regional dress and holding a musical instrument., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000014; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Women; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Palestine; Regional/National Dress; Musical Instruments; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Woodwind Instruments; Head Covers/Veils; Embroidery; Costumes
- (No. 44) Ibn El Sioud Bedouins (two duplicate portraits of two men, one holds a gun)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000015; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Men; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Guns; Weapons; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Canes/Walking Sticks; Bedouins; Palestine
- (No. 46) A Bedouin in his happy mood (a portrait of a man wearing regional dress (linked ref17,19,56)). Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000016; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Postcards; Individual Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Bedouins; Facial Hair
- (No. 46) A Bedouin in his happy mood (a portrait of a man wearing regional dress (linked ref16,19,56)). Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000017; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Men; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Palestine; Bedouins
- A view of masoned stairs leading to the Pool of Siloam (duplicate Ref48)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000018; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Water; Siloam/Silwan; Religious Sites
- (No. 46) A Bedouin in his happy mood (a portrait of a man wearing regional dress (linked ref16,17,56)). Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000019; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Men; Bedouins; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Palestine
- (No. 50) Hebron with the minerets of its great mosque (duplicate Ref21) [original spelling maintained]., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000020; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Buildings; Architecture; Mosques; Religious Sites; Hebron/Al-Khalil; Mountains/Hills
- (No. 50) Hebron with the minerets of its great mosque (duplicate Ref20) [original spelling maintained]., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000021; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Landscapes; Mosques; Religious Sites; Buildings; Architecture; Mountains/Hills; Hebron/Al-Khalil
- (No. 48) A 110 years old Jew of Tiberias (a portrait of a man with beard)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000022; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Palestine; Canes/Walking Sticks
- (No. 53) A Bedouin and his pride (two duplicate portraits of the same man posed with two horses (linked Ref6))., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000023; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Individual Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Horses; Animals; Bedouins; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Palestine
- (No. 63) The Fountain of Khalifa Omar (a view of the Fountain of Khalifa Omar, with the Al-Aqsa Mosque in the background (duplicate Ref26,27))., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000024; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Architecture; Mosques; Fountains; Religious Sites; Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Jerusalem; Buildings
- (No. 57) Steps leeding to the Christ's of the Holy Sepulchre (three men near the staircase leading to the Church of the Holy Sepulchre) [original spelling maintained]., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000025; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Streets/Roads; Churches; Religious Sites; Men; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Priests/Clergymen; Boys; Children; Head Covers/Veils; Jerusalem
- (No. 63) The Fountain of Khalifa Omar (a view of the Fountain of Khalifa Omar, with the Al-Aqsa Mosque in the background (duplicate Ref24,27))., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000026; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Mosques; Religious Sites; Fountains; Architecture; Buildings; Jerusalem
- (No. 63) The Fountain of Khalifa Omar (a view of the Fountain of Khalifa Omar, with the Al-Aqsa Mosque in the background (duplicate Ref24,26))., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000027; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Fountains; Mosques; Religious Sites; Architecture; Buildings; Jerusalem; Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā
- (No. 67) Tyropean Valley (Dome of the Rock) (duplicate Ref29,30)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000028; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Mosques; Mountains/Hills; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Religious Sites; Architecture; Buildings; Jerusalem
- (No. 67) Tyropean Valley (Dome of the Rock) (duplicate Ref28,30)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000029; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Architecture; Buildings; Mosques; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Mountains/Hills; Jerusalem
- (No. 67) Tyropean Valley (Dome of the Rock) (duplicate Ref28,29)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000030; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Mosques; Religious Sites; Architecture; Buildings; Jerusalem
- (No.105) House of Simon the Tanner (a portrait of a person sitting on the niche of a building) [location unconfirmed]., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000031; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Architecture; Buildings; Men; Jerusalem; Women; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Religious Sites
- (No. 73) Gethsemany (a view of the Garden of Gethsemane (duplicate Ref48))., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000032; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Gardens; Gethsemane, Jerusalem; Religious Sites; Men
- (No. 74) The Chapel of the Slaughter of the Infants (two views of the Chapel of the Milk Grotto (duplicate Ref59))., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000033; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Religious Sites; Churches; Bethlehem; Lanterns/Lamps; Paintings; Religious Imagery; Chapel of the Milk Grotto of Our Lady
- (No. 81) The tombs of St. James and Zachariah in the valley of Jehoshaphat., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000034; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Architecture; Buildings; Tombs/Mausoleums; Religious Sites; Jerusalem; Mountains/Hills
- (No. 84) Road leading to Mount Zion., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000035; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Mount Zion/Jabal Sahyoun, Jerusalem; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Streets/Roads; Men; Women
- (No. 85) The site where the Crown of Thorns was placed on Christ's head (a view of the Chapel of the Derision in the Church of the Holy Sepulchre)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000036; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Churches; Religious Sites; Religious Crosses; Architecture; Jerusalem
- (No. 27) The Mountains of Gilead behind the River Jordan (linked Ref10)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000037; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Rivers; Jordan River; Mountains/Hills; Palestine; Water; Landscapes
- (No. 16) The Ruins of Cesarea (a woman carrying a child at the beach at the beach at Qisarya/Cesarea (duplicate Ref8, 58))., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000038; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Caesarea/Qisarya; Coast; Beaches; Water; Women; Children; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
- (No. 87) A Bedouin girl (three duplicate portraits of a Bedouin woman)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000039; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Women; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Palestine; Jewelry
- (No.97) A Monastery in the rocks, kedron valley (a monastery in the Kidron Valley)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000040; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Landscapes; Buildings; Architecture; Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Kidron Valley; Monasteries/Convents
- (No. 100) Ain karim (a view of a road leading to Ein Karem)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000041; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Mountains/Hills; Ein Karem, Jerusalem
- A view of the Mahmoudiya Mosque in Jaffa., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000042; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Jaffa; Buildings; Architecture; Mosques; Religious Sites; Water; Mediterranean Sea; Seas; Tel Aviv/Tall ʾabīb
- (No. 109) David's Tower (the Tower of David)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000043; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Buildings; Religious Sites; Forts/Castles; Jerusalem
- (No. 112) Pool of Hezekiah (duplicate Ref45)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000044; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Religious Sites; Architecture; Buildings; Water; Jerusalem; Churches; Mosques; Religious Crosses; Hezekiah's Pool/Birkat Hammam el-Batrak
- (No. 112) Pool of Hezekiah (duplicate Ref44)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000045; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Water; Churches; Mosques; Buildings; Architecture; Religious Sites; Religious Crosses; Jerusalem; Hezekiah's Pool/Birkat Hammam el-Batrak
- (No. 110) Tower of Antonia (colonnade on the Temple Mount (duplicate Ref57))., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000046; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Architecture; Buildings; Jerusalem; Men; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Religious Sites
- (No. 114) Foundations of tower of Antonia (a view of the surrounding area of the Temple Mount and the Al-Ghawanimah Minaret)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000047; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Buildings; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Jerusalem; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Religious Sites
- Left: (No. 73) Gethsemany (a view of the Garden of Gethsemane (duplicate Ref32)). Right: masoned stairs leading to the Pool of Siloam (duplicate Ref18)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000048; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Religious Sites; Gardens; Water; Gethsemane, Jerusalem; Men; Siloam/Silwan; Religious Sites
- (No. 115) Cadi Burhan. ed. din's Pulpit (three duplicate portraits of a man at the Pulpit of the Cadi Borhan ed-Din)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000049; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Men; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Jerusalem; Buildings; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
- Two views showing the entrance to Christ's Tomb in the Church of the Holy Sepulchre (duplicate Ref62)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000050; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Tombs/Mausoleums; Religious Crosses; Lanterns/Lamps; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Churches; Religious Sites; Jerusalem
- A landscape of a beach with palm trees in Haifa, with Mt. Carmel in the background., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000051; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Palm Trees; Coast; Beaches; Water; Mountains/Hills; Haifa; Sea of Galilee/Lake Tiberias; Mount Carmel /Al-Karmil
- (No. 117) Street in Jerusalem., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000052; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Architecture; Jerusalem; Postcards
- (No. 116) Mount Zion., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000053; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Mount Zion/Jabal Sahyoun, Jerusalem; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Churches; Architecture; Buildings; Religious Sites
- A man playing a flute under a tree with sheep nearby., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000054; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Men; Individual Portraits; Musical Instruments; Woodwind Instruments; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Goats; Animals; Countryside/Rural; Palestine
- A portrait of a man and boys with livestock., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000055; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Men; Hats; Boys; Regional/National Dress; Children; Head Covers/Veils; Cattle/Cows; Horses; Donkeys; Animals; Camels; Canes/Walking Sticks; Facial Hair; Mountains/Hills; Countryside/Rural; Palestine; Group Portraits
- (No. 46) A Bedouin in his happy mood (a portrait of a man wearing regional dress (linked ref16,17,19)). Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000056; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Studio Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Men; Individual Portraits; Palestine; Bedouins
- (No. 110) Tower of Antonia (colonnade on the Temple Mount (duplicate Ref46))., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000057; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Architecture; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Men; Jerusalem; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Religious Sites